Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-huu-thao-nguyen-021934165 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Advertising
Microsoft Office
Customer Service

Nguyen Huu Thao nguyen

Marketing manager

Vung Tau, Ba Ria-Vung Tau, Vietnam

Summary

Take advantages of waitress skills & experience and understanding of market to become a

professional Copywriter Staff after finishing university and bring a lot value to Customers.

From that, I will contribute to development of fan-page. I live in Ho Chi Minh City, but I can go back Vung Tau city from Thursday to Sunday.

Experience

Công Ty TNHH Đồng Gia Phúc Marketing Manager April 2023 - Present (2 years)

Đồng Gia Phúc (Home Hotel) Senior Marketing Executive January 2021 - Present (4 years 3 months)

- Vietnam
- Brand management of 3 brands (Home hotel, D cafe, Den lounge)
- Combine online and offline marketing in the same campaign
- Researching customer behavior
- Branding to introduce service for local customer
- Development and re
- Branding
- Reorganized CRM Developing customer care process Developing digital marketing channels
- o Website: planing layout, function, writing content, selecting image
- o Planning to post on Social Network
- o Facebook: witing, posting status, designing draft image.
- o Instargram: posting story, design simple images
- Developing marketing activation

GCOMM

Project Manager

May 2020 - Present (4 years 11 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

- Receiving customer information, evaluting brand positioning, summarizing information about customer needs
- Digital and media planning Participate in negotiation and bidding
- Project management, working with stakeholders

Elysian Minds Company in Singapore Marketing Analyst January 2018 - Present (7 years 3 months) Singapore

- Create, maintain, review plan and manage project schedules.
- Working with KOL and supplyer
- Design, negotiate and present projects with customers
- Research customer behavior
- Brand Positioning
- Work with web engineering, design, events,...

4U Tours Marketing Staff October 2017 - October 2021 (4 years 1 month) Vietnam

elite english school Marketing Lead January 2018 - September 2018 (9 months) Vietnam

Education

Paris Graduate School of Management

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services · (September 2020 - April 2022)

University of Greenwich

 \cdot (2016 - 2019)

ERC Institute

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Marketing · (2017 - 2018)

University of Greenwich

Bachelor's degree, International Business Management